Damjan Pjević,

a student at the School of Economics and Business

Contact damjan@pjevic.com Online presence www.pjevic.com linkedin.com/in/pjevic

PERSONAL STATEMENT

An ambitious, reliable and open-minded individual with a great passion in tech and business. With a Bachelors in Multimedia Engineering focused on Digital Communication, I am in pursuit of my master's degree in Business Informatics at the School of Economics and Business in Ljubljana. Experienced with working with the clients, public speaking and working in a team and with a working history in the fields of the computer software industry, event organisation, digital media and marketing.

SKILLS

ΙT Website management, mobile application

development, basics in telecommunications.

Programming: Java, JavaScript, Python, HTML & CSS,

WordPress.

Marketing & PR Content creation, verbal communication,

promotional events.

Slovenin C2, English C2, Serbian B2, Languages

German B1, Russian A1.

EXPERIENCES

Value Add Games

2019 - Now

Website manager & Content creator

- Helped in marketing with the launch of their most successful product.
- Re-established the online shop.
- Maintained the website and the online
- Assisted with sales

Chamber of Commerce and Industry of Slovenia

2019 - Now

Technical Assistant

- Independently overseeing technical aspect and providing support for online events with around 10 speakers and more than 100 participants carried out in English or Slovenian.
- Recorded and edited over 50 videos (presentations and reportages) for various events.

EESTEC - LC Ljubljana

2015 - 2016

Member & Multimedia coordinator

- As one of the Coordinators, success fully managed the PR group for EESTEC Competition for Android 2015 and reached out to more students than any year before.
- Took part in a week-long seminar in Istanbul, Turkey focused on Marketing and Multimedia.

EDUCATION

2020 - 2022 Business Informatics - Masters. School of Economics and Business.

University of Ljubljana, Slovenia

2015 - 2019 Multimedia Engineering - Bachelors.

Faculty of Electrical Engineering, University of Ljubljana, Slovenia

Hochschule für Kunst Bremen, Germany (Erasmus Exchange 2017)

Selected class projects

- Extension of the Pan-European Mobile **Emergency Application with extended**
- Using Android SDK created and designed a translation app for one of the Slovene dialects.

Extracurriculars

Took part in the BEST Summer Course in [2019]

> Wroclaw, Poland that focuses on company management and how technology and good marketing strategy can embrace its

success.

[2016 - 2019]Took part in various promotional events of

the faculty.

[2012 - 2015]Took part in three different YouthPass

exchanges all focused on international

Peer-to-Peer communication.

[2011 - 2015]High School Debate club.

AWARDS

[2017] Reached top 20 out of 350 global

teams in OnePlus Student Marketing

Challenge.

[2016] Regional winners in global competition

OSCE.

Peer to Peer: Challenging Extremism by a successfully developed and pitched tool

for challenging violent extremism.